现在，一开始，当这听起来似乎是个办法的时候，我们减少每一个传输的，
Now, at first glass, reducing the payload of each transfer, and
并且只有数据传输
only transmitting data when it's required seems like a sound approach.
您减少数据的传输量，这样网络中就有更少的数据。
You're reducing the amount of data being transferred, so that's less
那样就会有更少已经完成了设备上的数据存储处理的没用的工作。
data on the network. That's less superfluous work being done storing processing
在你没有真正的
data on the device. It's basically a case of putting off
知道你需要干什么之前，基本上都耽误着所有的工作。
any work, until you actually know you need to do it.
但事实证明相比于之前的大cookie模式下的全部工作，
But it turns out that this approach has it's drawbacks, compared
这种方法也有他的缺点。
to the big cookie model of all of that work up front.
所以，综上所述，这个还是一个更好的解决办法。但是让我们近距离观察这个大cookie
So, overall, this is a better solution. But let's take a closer look at the big
模板。要做到这一点，我们真的
cookie model. And to do that, we really
需要理解并且以cell radio状态机为基础。
need to understand the underlying cell radio state machine.